Finding Aid for Donald W. Riegle, Jr. papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Senatorial Papers, 1977-1994
  - Legislative, 1977-1994
    - 102nd Congress, 1991-1992
      - Health
        - Uninsured
          - Initiative task force (Box 62)
          - Key materials, 2 folders (Box 62)
          - Labor, Health and Human Services study (Box 62)
          - Michigan programs (Box 62)
          - Presidential candidates’ plans (Box 62)
          - Republican plan (Box 62)
          - State hearing (Box 62)
        - Universal care-State health care plans (Box 62)
        - Visit to Charlevoix health department-Briefing book (Box 62)
        - Working group material (Box 62)
        - Workshop on Medigap (Box 62)
      - Health Hearings-Music therapy-Special Committee on Aging (Box 62)
      - Heavy duty truck excise (Box 62)
      - Homeless Outreach Act of, 1990 (Box 62)
      - Human Resources
        - Appropriations (Box 62)
        - Children (Box 62)
      - Immigration
        - S.618 (Box 62)
        - Albania
          - Humanitarian assistance (Box 62)
          - Aisha Sabri case (Box 62)
      - Indian affairs (Box 63)
        - Lumbee tribe (Box 63)
        - Appropriation, Fiscal year, 1992; 4 folders (Box 63)
      - Iraq, Kurdish refugees-Bazi family (Box 63)
      - Israel-Letter of recognition (Box 63)
      - Harkin amendment (Box 63)
      - Job Training Partnership Act (Box 63)
      - King, Rodney, violence (Box 63)
      - Labor
        - General, 4 folders (Box 63)
        - Striker replacement bill (S.55) (Box 63)
        - Unemployment compensation
          - 1991 (Box 63)
          - Briefings (Box 63)
        - Workplace Fairness (S.55) (Box 63)
      - Legislative activities-Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - Legislative summaries (Box 63)
      - Legislative summary
        - 1988-1992 (Box 63)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 63)
      - Letters co-signed
        - 1991 (Box 63)
        - 1992 (Box 63)
      - Local exchange infrastructure-Modernization Act (S.2810) (Box 63)
      - Japan, Japanese diet (Box 63)
      - Maritime reform (Box 63)
      - Michigan
        - Auto plant closings (Box 63)
        - Die casters’ request (Box 63)
        - Gerber food donation to Russia (Box 63)
        - Indian affairs (Box 63)
        - Parts manufacturing (Box 63)
        - Regional offices-Miscellaneous (Box 63)
        - Savings and loan materials (Box 63)
        - Trade-Pending issues 23 (Box 64)
        - Trip, January 1991 (Box 64)
        - UAW (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - National Energy Security Act (S.1220) 2 (Box 64)
      - Nomination-Clarence Thomas (Box 64)
      - Parental and Medical Leave Act (Box 64)
      - Persian Gulf War
        - Burden-sharing resolution (Box 64)
        - Riegle statements (Box 64)
      - Private bills
        - Bartski, Erica (Box 64)
        - Frith, Martha (Box 64)
        - Kpadenou, Samson (Box 64)
      - Project Home Safe (Box 64)
      - Public Utility Holding Company Act (Box 64)
      - Rehabilitation act-National Federation of the Blind (Box 64)
      - Roth bill (S.583) (Box 64)
      - Savings Bonds (Box 64)
      - Seniors softball week (Box 64)
      - Social Security
        - Administration acquiescence policy (Box 64)
        - Attorney fees (Box 64)
        - Correspondence (Box 64)
        - Disability determination (Box 64)
        - Earnings test markup (Box 64)
        - Zebley-Supplemental Security Income (Box 64)
      - South Africa-Lifting of sanctions (Box 64)
      - Soviet Union-Baltic region (Box 64)
      - Space station (Box 64)
      - Superconducting super collider (Box 64)
      - Supplemental Security Income
        - AIDS bill (Box 64)
        - Homeless outreach (S.1451) (Box 64)
      - Surface transportation, 1991 (Box 64)
      - Surface Transportation Assistance Act
        - 1991 (Box 64)
        - Michigan issues (Box 64)
      - Tax
        - Adult home health care (Box 64)
        - Advertising (Box 64)
        - Automobile depreciation (Box 64)
        - Completed contract accounting (Box 64)
        - Double dipping (S.588) (Box 64)
        - Enterprise Zone bill (H.R.11) (Box 64)
        - Foundation report (Box 64)
        - Insurance, accelerated death benefits (Box 64)
        - Issues (Box 64)
        - Passive Foreign Investment Company (Box 64)
        - Real estate issues (Box 64)
        - Revenue Estimate Request (S.1911) (Box 65)
        - Tax Extension Act (S.936) (Box 65)
        - Taxes (Box 65)
      - Term limitations (Box 65)
      - Trade
        - Capital choices hearing
          - Competitiveness
            - Hearing
              - April 1992 (Box 65)
              - May / June 1992 (Box 65)
              - August 1992 (Box 65)
            - Policy council report (Box 65)
          - Japanese Auto Trade bill (S.2145) (Box 65)
          - North American Free Trade Agreement (Box 65)
          - Riegle speech, November 1992 (Box 65)
          - Zenith-Air Force (Box 65)
      - Transportation (Box 65)
      - United Arab Emirates (Box 65)
      - United Postal Service, 3 folders
        - Appropriations (Box 65)
        - Letter carriers (Box 65)
        - Supervisors (Box 65)
        - Third class mail (Box 65)
        - Workers (Box 65)
      - Veterans
        - Coin bill (Box 65)
        - Disabled American Veterans (Box 65)
        - Issues (Box 65)
        - Health care (Box 65)
        - POW/MIA
          - Flag bill (Box 65)
          - Senate Select Committee (Box 65)
      - Voting Rights Act amendment (Box 65)
      - Washington, D.C. statehood (Box 65)
      - Wright amendment (Box 65)
      - Yugoslavia (Box 65)
    - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994
      - Act for Microenterprise Development (Box 65)
      - Administrative-Legislative activity memos (Box 65)
      - Aging Committee (Box 65)
      - Aging
        - Senior Power Day (Box 65)
        - Social Security
          - Administration independence (Box 65)
          - Earnings test (Box 65)
          - Notch bill (Box 65)
          - Reform bill (Box 65)
          - Tax fight (Box 65)
          - Taxation (Box 65)
          - Trust fund-Off budget (Box 65)
      - Agriculture (Box 66)
        - Appropriations (Box 66)
        - Cherry dumping bill (Box 66)
        - Crop disaster (Box 66)
        - Disaster relief (Box 66)
        - Michigan Tech energy grants (Box 66)
        - Pesticides (S.2050) (Box 66)
        - Sausage exports to Korea (Box 66)
      - American Jobs Protection Act (Box 66)
      - Appropriations-District of Columbia (Box 66)
      - Auto bill (Box 66)
      - Auto caucus (Box 66)
      - Auto-General (Box 66)
      - Auto industry speech (Box 66)
      - Auto parts bill (Box 66)
      - Auto meeting, President Clinton (Box 66)
      - Auto-White House meeting (Box 66)
      - Base Closure Realignment Act (Box 66)
      - Bottle bill (Box 66)
      - Breaux/Packwood amendment (S.2111) (Box 66)
      - California Desert Protection Act (S.21) (Box 66)
      - Campaign finance reform (Box 66)
      - Car recycling (Box 66)
      - Cellular communication, Regularity parity (Box 66)
      - Children
        - Adoption subsidies (Box 66)
        - Child abuse (Box 66)
        - Dependent care block grant (Box 66)
        - Earned income tax credit (Box 66)
        - Wayne State letter (Box 66)
      - Clinton technology statement (Box 66)
      - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network, 3 folders (Box 66)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting bill (S.2120) (Box 66)
      - Correspondence (Box 66)
      - Countries-Topical
        - Russia (Box 66)
        - Poland (Box 66)
        - Romania (Box 66)
        - Rwanda (Box 66)
        - Singapore (Box 66)
        - Somalia (Box 66)
        - Crisis background (Box 66)
        - Relief efforts (Box 66)
        - South Africa (Box 66)
        - Syria (Box 66)
        - Turkey (Box 66)
        - Ukraine
          - Background (Box 66)
          - Chernobyl (Box 66)
          - Sixtieth anniversary of famine (Box 66)
      - Defense
        - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (Box 66)
        - Appropriations bill -- Fiscal year amendments, 1994 (Box 66)
        - Army Reserves (Box 66)
        - Authorization bill, Fiscal year, 1994
          - American metal casting consortium (Box 66)
          - Burden sharing (Box 66)
          - Gulf War Veterans (Box 66)
          - World Cup, Soccer (Box 66)
        - Authorization bill, Fiscal year, 1995
          - Amendments (Box 67)
          - Intelligence (Box 67)
          - National Guard (Box 67)
          - University research (Box 67)
        - Ballistic missile defense (Box 67)
        - Base Closure and Realignment Commission
          - General, 4 folders
            - Briefing book (Box 67)
            - Impact on schools (Box 67)
            - Update (Box 67)
        - Base closures (Box 67)
        - Base closing legislation (Box 67)
        - Battle Creek Veterans Administration Medical Center (Box 67)
        - Budget, Fiscal year, 1995; 3 folders (Box 67)
        - Central America (Box 67)
        - Concurrent pension and veterans’ disability (Box 67)
        - Conversion
          - Administration (Box 67)
          - Democratic task force (Box 67)
          - Formula bill (Box 67)
          - Implementation (Box 67)
          - Pell extension (Box 67)
          - Personnel issues (Box 67)
          - Republican task force (Box 67)
        - Countries
          - Armenia (Box 67)
          - Balkans (Box 67)
          - Baltics (Box 67)
          - Bosnia (Box 67)
          - China (Box 67)
          - Greece (Box 67)
          - Haiti (Box 67)
          - India (Box 67)
          - Indonesia/East Timor (Box 67)
          - Kashmir (Box 67)
          - Kosovo (Box 67)
          - Lebanon (Box 67)
        - Defense conversion (Box 67)
        - Down-sizing (Box 67)
        - Foreign aid (Box 67)
        - Gays in military (Box 67)
        - Gulf War Syndrome (Box 67)
        - Iraq-Christian refugees (Box 67)
        - K. I. Sawyer base closing (Box 68)
        - Key issues (Box 68)
        - Michigan
          - Ann Arbor Veterans Administration Hospital (Box 68)
          - Ground Wave Emergency Network (Box 68)
          - Gwinn schools (Box 68)
          - K. I. Sawyer closure (Box 68)
          - Selfridge (Box 68)
        - Nominations (Box 68)
        - Production act-Appropriations (Box 68)
        - Robert Juett case (Box 68)
        - Trident II missile (Box 68)
        - Women’s Vietnam Veterans Memorial (Box 68)
        - Wurtsmith base closing (Box 68)
      - Department of Energy-National Competitiveness Technology Partnership Act (S.473) (Box 68)
      - Detroit Port Authority trip to Bangkok (Box 68)
      - Department of Defense flat panel procurement (Box 68)
      - Driver’s Privacy Protection Act (S.1589) (Box 68)
      - Economic initiative-Clinton speech (Box 68)
      - Economic leadership strategy (Box 68)
      - Economic memos (Box 68)
      - Education
        - Briefing book for Paul Quinn (Box 68)
        - Chapter one audit data (Box 68)
        - Community college issues (Box 68)
        - Dear Colleague letters (Box 68)
        - Elementary and Secondary Education Act (H.R.6/S.1513) (Box 68)
        - Federal regulations on college 85/15 rule (Box 68)
        - Fiscal year, 1995 (Box 68)
        - Goals, 2000 (Box 68)
        - Headstart program (Box 68)
        - Impact aid (Box 68)
        - Improving America’s Schools Act (Box 68)
        - Incoming mail report (Box 68)
        - Independent colleges and universities (Box 68)
        - Issue letters, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Issue form letters (Box 68)
        - Library item encyclopedia-Form letters (Box 68)
        - Mail liaison with Riegle staff, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Michigan
          - Impact aid-Oscoda/Wurtsmith (Box 68)
          - Kalamazoo (Box 68)
          - Partnership for new education (Box 68)
          - School finance reform issue (Box 68)
          - Title XX (Box 68)
        - National Association of Gifted Children (Box 68)
        - National Service Trust Act (Box 68)
        - Olympic training centers amendment (Box 68)
        - Parkinson’s Research, Education, and Assistance Act (S.2294) (Box 68)
        - Reauthorization
          - 1994 (Box 68)
          - Elementary and secondary education programs (Box 68)
        - Robo letters (Box 68)
        - School-to-work Act (Box 68)
        - Student Loan Reform Act (S.920) (Box 68)
        - Student loan issue (Box 68)
      - Energy
        - Interior appropriations (Box 68)
        - Water appropriations (Box 68)
      - Environment (Box 69)
        - Appropriations letters (Box 69)
        - Cement kiln dust (Box 69)
        - China and Taiwan-World Wildlife Fund sanctions (Box 69)
        - Conagra Foods-Iraqi letters of credit (Box 69)
        - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (Box 69)
        - KMS Fusion, Inc. v. United States, 2 folders (Box 69)
        - Land Reuse Act (Box 69)
        - Michigan
          - Manistique River superfund (Box 69)
          - Ozone attainment (Box 69)
          - Ozone transport (Box 69)
          - Petoskey water (Box 69)
          - Reformulated gasoline (Box 69)
          - Resource Conversation and Recovery Act (S.976) (Box 69)
          - Superfund Reform Act (S.1834) (Box 69)
          - Ward Valley Land Transfer Act (S.2151) (Box 69)
          - Water Resources Development Act (Box 69)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission-Reform (Box 69)
      - Estonia (Box 69)
      - Export promotion guidelines (Box 69)
      - FBI Wiretap Access bill (S.2375) (Box 69)
      - Federal mandates (Box 69)
      - Federal prison industries-Furniture, 2 folders (Box 69)
      - Finance Committee-Amendments, Background, Fiscal year, 1995
        - Budget (Box 69)
        - Funds (Box 69)
      - Government Accounting Office study on business assistance (Box 69)
      - Garten nomination (Box 69)
      - Gift ban (Box 69)
      - Goal Bill (S.1150), 2000 (Box 69)
      - Government affairs
        - Correspondence (Box 69)
        - Hatch act (Box 69)
      - Headstart (S.1852) (Box 69)
      - Health
        - Abortion-Freedom of Choice act (Box 69)
        - Abortion reform (Box 69)
        - Academic health centers hearing (Box 69)
        - Administrative simplification bill (Box 69)
        - AIDS (Box 69)
        - Amendments (Box 70)
        - Area Agency on Aging (Box 70)
        - Association plans (Box 70)
        - Benefits (Box 70)
        - Briefings (Box 70)
        - Budget reconciliation (Box 70)
        - Care task force, 3 folders (Box 70)
        - Causes of rising costs hearing (Box 70)
        - Charts, Old and new (Box 70)
        - Children-Health care reform-Hearing (Box 70)
        - Children First (Box 70)
        - Children’s
          - Amendments (Box 70)
          - Health hearing (Box 70)
          - Integration (Box 70)
        - Childhood immunizations hearing (Box 70)
        - Clinton plan-Briefing book, 3 folders (Box 70)
        - Clinton plan draft (Box 70)
        - Committee on Labor hearing (Box 70)
        - Competitiveness hearing (Box 70)
        - Cost containment hearing (Box 70)
        - Deferred compensation (Box 70)
        - Dental (Box 70)
        - Displaced women (Box 70)
        - Early retirees-Mitchell plan (Box 70)
        - Excise tax on tobacco (Box 70)
        - Finance Committee hearing (Box 70)
        - Finance Committee on Health-Hearing (Box 70)
        - Finance hearing, 2 folders (Box 70)
        - Finance-Miscellaneous (Box 71)
        - Floor amendments on Mitchell (Box 71)
        - Ford issues (Box 71)
        - Foreign health care hearing (Box 71)
        - Fiscal year appropriations, 1994 (Box 71)
        - General Accounting Office study (Box 71)
        - General health benefits briefing book (Box 71)
        - General health stuff (Box 71)
        - Graduate medical education (Box 71)
        - Great Lakes summit (Box 71)
        - Health alliances hearing (Box 71)
        - Health Care America advisory board invite (Box 71)
        - Health care task force (Box 71)
        - Health care summit (Box 71)
        - Health care for non-working people-Hearing, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Health care reform (Box 71)
        - Health care bill of rights (Box 71)
        - Health initiatives (Box 71)
        - Health reform
          - Briefing book (Box 71)
          - Business (Box 71)
          - Finance Democrats (Box 71)
          - Michigan Update briefing book (Box 71)
          - Miscellaneous issues (Box 71)
          - Miscellaneous items (Box 71)
        - Hearing aids (Box 71)
        - Hearings in Michigan (Box 71)
        - Health issues, Miscellaneous (Box 71)
        - Hospice project (Box 71)
        - Hillary Clinton health event (Box 71)
        - Immunization bill (Box 71)
        - Immunization practices, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Immunization-Shalala event (Box 72)
        - Immunizations (Box 72)
        - Immunizations bill (S.733)
          - Background material (Box 72)
          - Bulk purchase (Box 72)
          - Every Child by Two (Box 72)
          - Hearing testimony, 2 folders (Box 72)
          - Issues, 3 folders (Box 72)
          - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Indoor air quality (Box 72)
        - Infant mortality commission (Box 72)
        - Information network/privacy of information (Box 72)
        - Insurance market reform hearing (Box 72)
        - Liberal coalition (Box 72)
        - Long-term care
          - Hearing (Box 72)
          - Medicare drug benefit-Finance hearing (Box 72)
          - Staff briefing (Box 72)
        - Low income (Box 72)
        - Mainstream bill (Box 72)
        - Malpractice reform (Box 72)
        - Medical malpractice (Box 72)
        - National health policy forum (Box 72)
        - Medical practice patterns hearing (Box 73)
        - Medicare
          - Ambulance (Box 73)
          - Drug bill, 2 folders (Box 73)
          - Institute for Mental Disease, 3 folders (Box 73)
          - Nursing home deposits (Box 73)
          - Qualified Medicare beneficiary (S.649), 2 folders (Box 73)
          - Respiratory care (Box 73)
        - Michigan
          - Analysis (Box 73)
          - Henry Ford health system (Box 73)
          - Issues, 2 folders (Box 73)
          - Briefing book, 2 folders (Box 73)
          - Issues for reform (Box 73)
          - Statistics (Box 73)
          - Upjohn (Box 73)
        - Mitchell bill (Box 73)
        - Mitchell list (Box 73)
        - National Institutes of Health-Reauthorization (S.1)
          - New generation devices (Box 73)
          - Notebooks, 5 folders
            - Notebooks folder 1 (Box 73)
            - Notebooks folders 2-5 (Box 74)
        - Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act-Physician referral (Box 74)
        - Pharmaceutical market place reform-Hearing (Box 74)
        - Pre-Medicare population alternative (Box 74)
        - Premiums and subsidies hearing
          - Part I (Box 74)
          - Part II (Box 74)
        - Price controls (Box 74)
        - Purchasing cooperatives (Box 74)
        - Qualified Medicare Beneficiary Program (Box 74)
        - Red Cross resolution (Box 74)
        - Reducing costs, Savings to business (Box 74)
        - Republican bill-Competition act (Box 74)
        - Retiree benefits hearing
          - 1993 (Box 74)
          - Briefing book, 1994 (Box 74)
        - Retiree health hearings (Box 74)
        - Retirees-Early benefits (Box 74)
        - Retirees’ health-Administration (Box 74)
        - Riegle Finance markup (Box 74)
        - Riegle health reform (Box 74)
        - Riegle letters, signed/co-signed, 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Robert Wood Johnson
          - Hearing (Box 74)
          - Briefing book (Box 74)
        - Rump proposal (Box 74)
        - Rural Indian health provision (Box 74)
        - Senior Power Day (Box 74)
        - Small business-Health care reform (Box 74)
        - Social problems and health care costs-Hearing (Box 75)
        - Speeches (Box 75)
        - Subcommittee on Workforce hearing (Box 75)
        - Supplemental Security Income/Medicare (Box 75)
        - Tax caps (Box 75)
        - Tax caps hearing, 2 folders (Box 75)
        - Transcripts (Box 75)
        - Tax gap (Box 75)
        - Tax on high cost plans (Box 75)
        - Trauma care (Box 75)
        - Uninsured
          - Mandates-Amendments (Box 75)
          - Health care coverage hearing (Box 75)
          - Retiree health proposition (Box 75)
        - Universal Coverage Coalition-Democrats’ meeting (Box 75)
        - Universal vaccine distribution programs (Box 75)
        - Virginia Finance Committee briefing (Box 75)
        - Washington Business Group on Health event (Box 75)
        - Women and children-Early implementation of subsidies (Box 75)
        - Women
          - Breast and cervical cancer program (Box 75)
          - HIV (Box 75)
        - Workplace wellness (Box 75)
      - Health America (S.1227)-Correspondence (Box 75)
      - Health reform
        - Early retirees-Mark-up Committee (Box 75)
        - Wayne County (Box 75)
      - Immigration
        - Bazi family case (Box 75)
        - German/American Day (Box 75)
        - International parental abduction bill (Box 75)
      - Indian education (Box 75)
      - Information Superhighway Bill (S.1822) (Box 75)
      - Infrastructure-Regan proposal (Box 75)
      - Jobs
        - Ford data (Box 75)
        - Memo (Box 75)
        - Memo to Riegle (Box 75)
        - Riegle charts (Box 75)
      - Judiciary
        - Crime bill-amendments (Box 75)
        - Ephedrine abuse (Box 75)
        - Federal prison industries (UNICOR) (Box 76)
      - Korea-Cooked sausage, Imports (Box 76)
      - Kuwait housing constructions (Box 76)
      - Labor
        - Apprenticeship (Box 76)
        - Employment non-discrimination (Box 76)
        - Striker replacement (Box 76)
        - Unemployment-Emergency compensation (S.382) (Box 76)
      - Laughter Corporation/Marujun (Box 76)
      - Legislative summary-Miscellaneous (Box 76)
      - Legislative update (Box 76)
      - Letters co-signed 3 (Box 76)
      - Lobby reform (Box 76)
      - Lobbying reform (Box 76)
      - Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Program (Box 76)
      - Malaysia-Webb Company project (Box 76)
      - Manufacturing and technology memos (Box 76)
      - MARITECH status (Box 76)
      - Michigan
        - Child care issues (Box 76)
        - Capital Access Fund (S.478, S.3222) (Box 76)
        - Detroit
          - G7 Summit (Box 76)
          - Immigration judge request (Box 76)
          - Metro radar (Box 76)
          - Metro South Access Road (Box 76)
          - Rail tunnel (Box 76)
        - Economic model (Box 76)
        - Empowerment zones (Box 76)
        - Ice cutter Mackinaw (Box 76)
        - Industrial aid and bonds (Box 76)
        - Plant closings (Box 76)
        - Sault Ste. Marie Senior Center (Box 76)
        - Staff activity reports, 2 folders (Box 76)
        - Transportation (Box 76)
      - Michigan State University-Center for Fundamental Materials Research (Box 76)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 76)
      - Motor and Equipment Manufacturers Association-Japan office (Box 76)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA)-Memos and letters (Box 76)
      - National Center for Manufacturing Sciences
        - Panetta letters and appropriations (Box 76)
        - Trailer (Box 76)
      - National Competitiveness Act (S.4) (Box 76)
      - National Cooperative Research Act extension (S.479) (Box 76)
      - National Corrections Officers Week (Box 76)
      - National Institute of Standards and Technology and Supply (Box 76)
      - National Treasury Employees Union (Box 76)